Guide to the Michael G. Shively papers,1976-1995.
Shively, Michael G. papers,1976-1995
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Michael G. Shively papers, 1976-1995.
7671
Michael G. Shively 1947-
18.6 cubic ft.
Manuscripts, printed materials, working files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Michael Shively's personal papers, including files from his work as Associate Director of the Center for Homosexual, Education, Evaluation, and Research (CHEER) at San Francisco State University, 1975-1980; his work for Liberation Publications Inc., which published the ADVOCATE, 1980-90; and his work at Damron Publishing since 1990.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Michael Shively's personal papers, including files from his work as Associate Director of the Center for Homosexual, Education, Evaluation, and Research (CHEER) at San Francisco State University, 1975-1980; his work for Liberation Publications Inc., which published the ADVOCATE, 1980-90; and his work at Damron Publishing since 1990.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Shively, Michael G.,1947-; Damron Company.
Titles:
Advocate (Los Angeles, Calif.)
Subjects:
Gays.; Gay liberation movement--United States.; Homosexuality--United States; Gay accommodations; Gays--Travel
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Box 7, folder 22 restricted until January 2051 or upon Pat Califia's death.
Box 17 restricted until John DeCecco's death or the year 2025.
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
SERIES LIST
Series I. CHEER
Boxes 1,17
Series II. Advocate/LPI
Boxes 2-6
Series III. Chronological Files/Correspondence
Boxes 7-15, 21-23
Series IV. Damron
Boxes 16, 18-21, 24-27, 29, 30
Series V. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. CHEER
  - C.H.E.E.R. Field Study, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - C.H.E.E.R. Letterhead and envelopes (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Journal of Homosexuality (JH) Letterhead and Envelopes (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Journal of Homosexuality, 1975-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sociobiology, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - NIMH Small Grants, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Continuation Grant: Adaptation of Aging Men & Women, June 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Components of Sexual Identity (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Michael Shively Graduate School Materials (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Faghagging Article (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Thesis: The Identification of the Social Sex-Role Stereotypes (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Handballing Short Story, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Thesis: The Effects of Social Sex-Role Stereotypes and Sexual Orientation on Psychotherapeutic Outcomes, Petra Liljestrand, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sexual Orientation Materials, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Sexual Orientation Survey- SFSU, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sexual Orientation Survey- SFSU- Work Folder, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sexual Orientation Survey- SFSU- Psych 673, Fall 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Sexual Orientation Survey- SFSU- Psych 674; Shively- Research on the Aspects & Dimensions of Sexual Orientation Coder's Tabulation Booklet, Fall 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Sexual Orientation Survey- SFSU- Psych 770, Fall 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Sexual Orientation Survey- SFSU, May 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Grant Application: Developing the Homosexual Identity, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Sniffin' to Switchin'": Sexual Assault in the San Francisco County Jail (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Rape in the County Jail, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Supplemental Report of Project Activities and Plans: Study and Prevention of Sexual Assault in the San Francisco County Jail, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Coding Manual for Sheriff's Department Personnel Interview Schedule: Study and Prevention of Sexual Assault in the San Francisco County Jail, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Informed Consent Form: Study and Prevention of Sexual Assault in the San Francisco County Jail (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Femininity in India and America (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - The Butch Camp: A Study of Communication in Two Gay Bars of Denver (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Classification Protocol Article (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Social Sex-Role Stereotypes (SSRS) and Assault in Jails (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Report to Granting Agency on Progress of Study and Prevention of Sexual Assault in the San Francisco County Jail (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Development of Training Package for Study and Prevention of Sexual Assault in the San Francisco County Jail (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - An Information Package for Identifying and Protecting Potential Inmate-Victims of Sexual Assault (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Study of Recorded Sex Assaults in the San Francisco County Jail (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Relationship of Previous Incarceration to the Prediction of Sexual Assault Victims in the San Francisco County Jail (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Evaluation of Screening Procedures for Study and Prevention of Sexual Assault in the San Francisco County Jail (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Correctional Institutes: General (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Proposal: Study and Prevention of Sexual Assault in the San Francisco County Jail (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Study and Prevention of Sexual Assault in the San Francisco County Jail: Three Month Trial Implementation Period (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bibliography: Study and Prevention of Sexual Assault in the San Francisco County Jail (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Characteristics Associated with Male Homosexuality within a State Correctional Population, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Study and Prevention of Sexual Assault in the San Francisco County Jail: Results of Profile Study (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - CACUHO Presentation, April 1981 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence and Files Re: Book Manuscript with John P. DeCecco, 5/82-9/85 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and Files Re: Book Manuscript with John P. DeCecco, 10/85-10/93 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript: The Heterosexual and Homosexual Identities: The Normalization of Sexual Relationships, by John P. DeCecco and Michael G. Shively, (preface, ch. 1-2) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - The Heterosexual..., (ch. 3-5) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - The Heterosexual..., (ch. 6-7) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - The Heterosexual..., (ch. 8) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - The Heterosexual..., (ch. 9-10) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - The Heterosexual..., (ch. 11-12) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The Heterosexual..., (ch. 13-14) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - The Heterosexual..., (ch. 15-16, pg. 34) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - The Heterosexual..., (ch. 16, pg. 35- ch. 17) (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - The Heterosexual..., (ch. 18-19, pg. 59) (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - The Heterosexual..., (ch. 19, pg. 60-ch. 20) (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - The Heterosexual..., (ch. 21-Bibliography) (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - C.H.E.E.R. CLIB Team, New York photo album, Fall 1979-Spring 1980 (Box 23)
- Series II. Advocate/LPI
  - Computer Services, Shively's Job Description: Hardware and Operating Environment Maintenance Technician, Business Services Department, 8/88-11/88 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ADR Operations, 11/88-6/89 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Computer Committee, 5/88-8/89 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Production, 1/89-6/89 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - STR Central Stores MLM/MLS, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Downsizing (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Move, 12/88-6/89 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Art, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - PDC Operations, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - AVS Audiovisuals, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - EDT Editorial, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - URS, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Inventory, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lawyers, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - MKT Marketing, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Blank Model Releases (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Legal, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Legal, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Masthead, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Masthead, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Copier/Reader, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Malibu Man (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Model/Photographer Information, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Ongoing Projects Lists, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - PRN, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - PDC (Publishers Distributing Company), 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - PDC, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - PDC, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - PDC, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - PDC, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - PDC Reorganization, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - PDC Reorganization, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - The Source (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Special Information, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - STR Central Stores, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Rate Card Info (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - LPI Personnel Policies and Procedures, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Display Advertising and Computer Software (PTC), 11/86-4/87 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Computer Projects, 8/85-6/87 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Computer Projects, 8/85-6/87 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - ACC- Accounting, 3/88-2/89 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - ACC- Accounting, 2/89-4/89 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - ACC- Accounting, 4/89-12/89 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - ADR- Display Advertising Sales, 2/88-8/88 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - ADR- Display Advertising Sales, 8/88-1/89 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - ADR- Display Advertising Sales, 2/89-7/89 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - ADR- Display Advertising Sales, 7/89-12/89 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - ART, 4/88-2/89 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - ART, 2/89-9/89 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - AVS- Audiovisual, 5/88-2/89 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - BUS- Business Materials, 10/87-9/88 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - BUS- Business Materials, 10/88-2/89 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - BUS- Business Materials, 3/89-4/89 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - BUS- Business Materials, 5/89-12/89 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Computer Committee, 3/87-9/88 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Computer Committee, 10/88-4/89 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Computer Committee, 5/89-7/89 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Computer Committee, 9/88-8/89 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Computer Committee, 10/88-3/89 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Adviser Book (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - PDC- Distribution, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - PDC- Old Materials/Back of File, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - PDC- Old Materials/Back of File, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - PDC- Old Materials/Back of File, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Production Department, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Production Department, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Production Department, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Production Department, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Production Department, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Production Department, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - STR, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Warehouse (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Van Purchase Project (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - TYP- Typesetting, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - SUB- Subscriptions, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - STR, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - STR, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - STR, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - STR, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - STR, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Cash Report, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Construction Resources (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - OOP/CEO- Office of the CEO, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - CLS- Classifieds, 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Comstock, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Comstock, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Peter Cummings, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - EDT- Editorial, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - COR- Corporate Affairs, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Computer Services, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence (Thom Bean), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Executive Committee Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Executive Committee Meetings/COR Old, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Meetings/COR Old, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Meetings/COR Old, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - EDT- Editorial "Old", 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - EDT "Old", 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - EDT "Old", 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - EDT "Old", 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - COR, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - COR, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - COR, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - COR, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Insurance Claims, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Business Services/RICOH Copier Conflict, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - The Move (1 May 1986), 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Expense Vouchers (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Frank Vinci, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 02 Pebble Pages, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 10 The Advocate, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Trades/Display Advertising (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Display Advertising- Frank/Niles Information, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Executive Materials- GMG Task Force, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Executive Materials- Long-Term Illness Project, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Executive Materials- Computerization, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Executive Materials- Memos by Date, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Executive Materials- Correspondence by Date, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Executive Materials- General Management Group, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - General File- Budget Information, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - General File- Correspondence by Date, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - General File- Memos by Date, 1986-1988 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Business Services- General Information, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Business Services- Correspondence by Date, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Business Services- Personnel Information, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Business Services- Memos by Date, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Market Space- Correspondence by Date (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Market Space- Memos by Date, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Classifieds- General Information (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Classifieds- Memos by Date, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Classifieds- Correspondence by Date, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Friction- Advertising Information, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Friction- General (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Advocate Men- Video Project, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Advocate Men- Video Reviews, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Advocate Men- Correspondence by Date, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Malibu Sales- General Information, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Malibu Sales- Budget Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Malibu Sales- Shipping Materials Information, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Malibu Sales- Advertising Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Malibu Sales- Organization Information, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Malibu Sales- Trade Departments, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Malibu Sales- P-Flag, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Malibu Sales- Promotional Materials, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Malibu Sales- Video Duplication Information, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Malibu Sales- Off Site, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Malibu Sales- Wholesale Inquiries, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Malibu Sales- Correspondence by Date, 1985-1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Malibu Sales- HIM Vitamins, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Malibu Sales- Computerization, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Malibu Sales- Forms & Invoices (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Malibu Sales & Malibu Man Sales Catalogs, 1986-1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Malibu Sales- Memos by Date, 5/85-11/87 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Malibu Sales- Memos by Date, 11/87-1/88 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Malibu Sales- Memos by Date, 6/87-5/88 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Malibu Sales- Memos by Date, 2/88-4/89 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Malibu Sales- Memos by Date, 5/88-1/99 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Morrow Computer Materials- Running Under CPM (Enclosed Memorandum from Michael Shively), 1984-1985 (2001) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Executive Retreat Materials- San Diego (photos included), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Executive Retreat Materials- Palm Springs (photos included), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Executive Retreat Materials- Santa Barbara (photos included), 1989 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Executive Retreat Materials- Corporate Offices- Hollywood Boulevard, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Advocate/LPI Staff Photographs (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Series III. Chronological Files/Correspondence
  - Joel Hencken Correspondence, 4/76-10/77 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Joel Hencken Correspondence, 12/77-7/82 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence I, 1/76-10/78 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence I, 5/78-12/78 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence II, 12/78-4/80 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - New York Correspondence- C.H.E.E.R. Personnel, 10/79-2/80 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - New York Correspondence- Randy Jones, 10/79- 3/80 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - New York Correspondence- Stuart Kellogg, 9/79-4/80 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - New York Correspondence- General and Photos, 1/79-2/80 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - New York Correspondence- Friends #1, 10/79-1/80 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - New York Correspondence- Friends #1, 10/79-1/80 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - New York Correspondence- Friends #2, 1/80-2/80 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - New York Correspondence- Friends #2, 2/80 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence III, 5/79-7/80 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence IV, 7/80-12/80 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence V, 12/80-5/81 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence VI, 5/81-10/81 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence VI, 10/81-12/81 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence VII, 11/81-7/82 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Wendell Ricketts Correspondence, 7/82-8/82 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence VIII, 7/82-11/82 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Pat Califia, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence IX, 11/82-2/83 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence X, 2/83-7/83 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence X, 8/83 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence XI, 8/83-2/84 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence XI, 8/83-2/84 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence XII, 3/84-9/84 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence XII, 3/83-9/84 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence XIII, 9/84-11/84 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence XIV, 12/84-4/85 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence XV, 4/85-10/85 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence XVI, 11/85-10/86 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence XVI, 11/85-10/86 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence XVI, 11/85-10/86 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence XVII, 10/86-5/88 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence XVII, 10/86-5/88 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence XVIII, 5/88 mixed 10/88 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence XIX, 8/88 mixed 12/88 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence XIX, 8/88 mixed 12/88 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence XX (20), 12/88-6/89 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence XX (20), 12/88-6/89 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence XXI (21), 7/89-12/89 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence XXI (21), 7/89-12/89 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence XXII (22), 12/89 mixed 2/90 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence XXII (22), 12/89 mixed 2/90 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence XXIII (23), 12/89 mixed 6/90 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence XXIII (23), 12/89 mixed 6/90 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence XXIV (24), 6/90-3/91 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence XXIV (24), 6/90-3/91 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence XXIV (24), 6/90-3/91 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence XXV (25), 4/91 mixed 11/91 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence XXV (25), 4/91 mixed 11/91 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence XXVI (26), 8/91 mixed 2/92 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence XXVI (26), 8/91 mixed 2/92 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence XXVII (27), 2/92-6/92 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence XXVIII (28), 6/92-2/93 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence XXVIII (28), 6/92-2/93 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence XXVIII (28), 6/92-2/93 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence XXIX (29), 3/93-12/93 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence XXIX (29), 3/93-12/93 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence XXIX (29), 3/93-12/93 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence XXX (30), 1/94-12/94 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence XXX (30), 1/94-12/94 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence XXX (30), 1/94-12/94 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence XXXI (31), 12/94-5/95 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence XXXI (31), 12/94-5/95 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence XXXII (32), 5/95-7/95 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence XXXIII (33), 7/95 mixed 10/95 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence XXXIV (34), 8/95 mixed 12/95 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence XXXIV (34), 8/95 mixed 12/95 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence XXXV (35), 12/95-3/96 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence XXXV (35), 12/95-3/96 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence XXXVI (36), 3/96-5/96 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence XXXVI (36), 3/96-5/96 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence XXXVII (37), 5/96-6/96 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence XXXVIII (38), 6/96-7/96 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence XXXVIII (38), 6/96-7/96 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence XXXIX (39), 7/96 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence XXXIX (39), 7/96 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence XXXX (40), 7/96-9/96 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence XXXX (40), 7/96-9/96 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence XXXXI (41), 9/96-10/96 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence XXXXI (41), 9/96-10/96 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence XXXXII (42), 10/96 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence XXXXIII (43), 11/96 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence XXXXIII (43), 11/96 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence XXXXIV (44), 11/96-12/96 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence XXXXV (45), 12/96-1/97 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence XXXXVI (46), 1/97-2/97 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence XXXXVII (47), 2/97 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence XXXXVIII (48), 2/97-3/97 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence XXXXIX (49), 3/97-4/97 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence L (50), 4/97 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence LI (51), 4/97-5/97 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence LII (52), 5/97-6/97 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence LIII (53), 6/97-7/97 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence LIV (54), 7/97 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence LV (55), 7/97-8/97 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence LVI (56), 8/97-9/97 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence LVII (57), 9/97 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Kreemah Ritz signed "Sylvester" Retrospective Poster, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - "Sylvester" Retrospective Flyers (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence LVIII (58), 9/97 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence LIX (59), 9/97-10/97 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence LX (60), 10/97-11/97 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence LXI (61), 11/97 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence LXII (62), 11/97-12/97 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence LXIII (63), 12/97 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence LXIV (64), 1/98 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence LXV (65), 1/98-2/98 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence LXVI (66), 2/98 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence LXVII (67), 2/98-3/98 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence LXVIII (68), 3/98-4/98 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence LXIX (69), 4/98 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence LXX (70), 4/98-5/98 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence LXXI (71), 5/98 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence LXXII (72), 5/98-6/98 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence LXXIII (73), 6/98-7/98 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Thesis Draft: Proofreading in the Dark and Other Stories, by Wendell Ricketts, 5/13/98 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence 74, 7/98 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 75, 7/98-8/98 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence 76, 8/98 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence 77, 8/98-9/98 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence 78, 9/98 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence 79, 9/98-10/98 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence 80, 10/98 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence 81, 10/98-11/98 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence 82, 11/98 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence 83, 11/98-12/98 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence 84, 12/98 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence 85, 12/98-1/99 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence 86, 1/99-2/99 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence 87, 2/99 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence 88, 2/99-3/99 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence 89, 3/99-4/99 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Draft Copy: Melting Point, by Pat Califia, 6/8/92 (Box 14, Folder 1)